Kushagra Shrivastava

Discord: @protonicgod Website: protonicgod.me

DESCRIPTION

I am Kushagra and I go by Protonicgod, I am a seasoned Discord Community Manager with over 5 years of experience specializing in community moderation and management. I have worked with brands and content creators with over 20,000,000 followers. Being the owner of India's largest advertisement server, I am committed to use my experience to build and nurture thriving communities whilst promoting growth.

EXPERIENCE

Associate Community Manager

Feb 2023 - Present

♦ ModSquad (Feb 2024 - Present): Spearheaded the development of highly engaged online communities for leading multinational tech companies. Conducted in-depth research to identify potential community partners and collaborated with cross-functional teams to enhance user experience, driving significant community growth. Successfully managed communities with up to 1,000,000 members.

Discord Community Manager

Sept 2019 - Present

- ♦ Makeshift Project (May 2024 Present): Created and managed with the Makeshift Project (1.3 million on Youtube) on their official Discord server for their fans.
- ♦ Code Social (May 2023 Present): Grew community membership from 300 to 1,200 members in 5 months (300% growth) and implemented effective strategies to attract and retain new members. Promoted to Co-Founder in Apr 2024 for exemplary performance as a Core Team member.
- ♦ Sponic Advertisements (June 2022 Sept 2024): Owner of India's biggest advertisement server (13,000). Managed a team of moderators and other teams to keep the server running smoothly and provide a positive experience for all users.
- ♦ Battlechest (Dec 2023 May 2024): Oversaw the successful coordination and execution of gaming tournaments for a thriving 16,000-member community. Introduced three over-the-top programs for community, which promote healthy lifestyle habits including reading.
- ♦ Jobs, Hiring & Market (Oct 2023 Mar 2024) : Managed one the biggest freelancer platforms on Discord with over 11,000 members. Successfully revamped the server to automize the job postings as well as verified reports regarding scams.
- ♦ E-Girls Social (Sept 2023 Nov 2023): Mentored and trained new moderators, passing on knowledge and skills to help them succeed in their roles in the large and hyperactive community (200,000 members).

Discord Community Moderator

Sept 2019 - Present

- ♦ Sexy.AI (Sept 23 Present, 19,000 members): A leading NSFW AI image generation platform.
- ♦ **BeluGANG** (Aug 22 Sept 22, 700,000 members) : Official Discord server of Beluga, content creator with 10,000,000 followers.
- ♦ Hideout (May 22 Jun 22, 135,000 members) : One of the most famous and active Discord servers.
- ♦ Slogo (Aug 21 Apr 22, 300,000 members) : Official Discord server of Slogo, or Slogoman, a gaming content creator with over 11,000,000 followers.

EDUCATION

Samrat Ashok Technological Institute

Bachelor of Technology in Internet of Things (IoT)

Vidisha, India

Email: hi@protonicgod.me

Linkedin: Kushagra Shrivastava

SKILLS

Discord, Notion, ClickUp, Asana, Slack, Adobe Suite (Photoshop, Premiere Pro, After Effects, Audition), Google Workspace (Sheets, Docs, Slides), Microsoft Office Suite (Word, Excel, Powerpoint)